hello everyone welcome to my
short and sweet presentation on icici
lombard first of all let me introduce
about myself
my name is shirak sangma from west garo
hills
currently i'm pursuing my bachelor of
business administration
in martin luther christian university
shillong
now without any wasting time
let us proceed to that presentation
here are the objectives of the
topic first
introduction second body third
conclusion
this is the introduction slide now let
me read
about the slide icici
lombard is a general insurance the
largest private sector
known as life insurance in india the
headquarters is in mumbai
the company was founded in the year of
it was founded as a joint venture with
icici bank limited
they mainly offer credit insurance
products and services
like motor insurance health insurance
travel insurance energy insurance
personal accident insurance marine
insurance
liability insurance and home insurance
next slide continuation
the number of employees is 890
as march 2020 it is engaged
in providing various general insurance
products and services
it is the largest private sector known
live in shooter in india
based on gross diet premium in income
in fiscal 2017.
they also provide insurance claims
management
investment management services through
multiple
distribution channels
they provide services to small and
medium enterprises
state and central government through
various channels
such as agents brokers bank insurance
and online platforms
now we have reached to the body of the
topic
product and services i see ici lumber
motor insurance
first let me read that i see ici lumber
health insurance about
a longboard health insurance there are
some of the types
like icici lombard complete health
insurance
health booster araguas and gibney policy
now let me bleep about that
motor insurance
motor insurance covers loss or damage
to your vehicle against natural
calamities
personal accidents loss or damage to
your vehicle against manmade calamities
now i will brief about
the types of health insurance first i
see
i say longboard complete health
insurance
icici lumbar complete health insurance
provides you with extensive coverage
during a medical emergency
l and health booster health booster
policy makes your health insurance more
important
it is the super top-up plan that acts as
a breakup in case your best plan gets
exhausted now last one
aragua sanjivani policy
icici lumber this policy is the health
plan that
takes care of your basic health care
needs
it comes at an affordable premium
with flexible some insult options
starting from
one legs
this is a continuation part of the body
here i see is a lumbar home insurance
and i see ici lumbar property in
students
now let me talk about
lumber home insurance home insurance
coverage furniture electronics and other
contents
and lumbar property insurance co
provides either
property protection coverage or
liability
coverage for property owners
and the next slide is what are the top
reasons to buy
icici longboard health insurance plans
from the slide we can look first point
is no limit on hospitals
room rent and second point is help a pre
free health checkup every year third one
wellness program
for lime lifelong renewability
now let me brief about first point no
limit on hospitals room rent
icici lombard complete health insurance
policy
has no sub limits on hospitals room rent
and second point free health checkup
every year
icici longboard complete health
insurance
plan provides you with a complimentary
health checkup coupon coupon
after a policy year and third
point is wellness program wellness
program intends
to promote innocent device and reward
you
for your healthy behavior through
various wellness
program and last point is
lifelong renewability medical expenses
incurred by you immediately up to 60
days
before and up to 90 days after your
hospitalization cover
up to some insult
now next slide is
financials of icici
lumber
gross return premium gwp rupees
135.92 billion
a market share of 12.6 percent
tax increase from rupees 15.97 billion
in fiscal 2019 to rupees
16.97 billion in
fiscal 2020.
finance years of icici icici general
gross written premium
was 135.92 billion in fiscal 2020.
icici lumber let the private players
including stan
dallon help insurers in the general
insurance
sector with a market share of 12.6
percent
and had a overall industry market share
of
seven seven point zero percent
ici lumbered profit before tax increase
from 15.98 billion fiscal
2019 to 16.97 billion
in fiscal 2020 icici lombard's
profit tax increase from 10.
billion in fiscal 2019 to 11.94 billion
in fiscal 2020.
now we have reached to the conclusion
part
icici lumbered company is a good
insurance company limited
the company offers insurance for motor
health
home and student travel they provide the
benefits
benefits and the services like quick
claim settlement
and roadside assistance etc
icici lombard is a good insurance
company limited
it is one of the leading private sector
general industry company
in india offering insurance coverage for
motor insurance
health home and student trouble
and more the various policies that icici
lumber
may introduce from time to time
icici lombard is not like other company
because it provides the benefits and the
services
like crew claim settlements roadside
assistance
depreciation weber
4300 plus garages offering cashless
service and 24 into 7 claim assistance
customer
service
now we have come to an end
thank you for patiently watching my
short and sweet
presentation on icici lombard
once again thank you